genoahc.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy describes the information we gather, how we share that information and what we do to protect your information.

 **What personal information do we collect?**  
As set forth in more details below, genoahc.com ("genoahc" or "We") collects personal information that you provide when using the genoahc website ("Site"). This information includes registered email, password, your first, last name, IP address, the date and time, browser and operating system, the URL you requested, your paypal email, your paypal shipping address and other information. Some examples of why we need this information include assisting in pre orders, delivery, payment verification, promotions and newsletters, statistics on website use to aid in improving our customer experience and offering the most popular products. To contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have elected not to receive promotional communications in connection with this website. If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, you can click the unsubscribe link.

You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of certain features, such as "Save for Later," "Address Book" and the other genoahc services. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

 **How do we collect the information?  ** **  
Purchase Information**  
When you make a purchase from genoahc, we collect your name and payment method information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, billing address, shipping address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s).

When you create an account at genoahc, you can choose to save your billing information in "My genoahc." You can also save one or more shipping addresses in Your genoahc Address Book. You may change or delete this saved information anytime. Simply go to My genoahc. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.Services Account Information.

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the genoahc services. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at genoahc.

 **Cookies and Other Computer Information**  
When you visit genoahc, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit this Site so we can enhance and customize your online purchase experience.

You can choose to browse on genoahc without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of this Site. These features include storing your shopping cart for later use and, in the future, providing a more personalized shopping experience. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to genoahc. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to this Site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on this Site and to track and measure performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on this Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) Will be received by or shared with these third parties.

As you browse genoahc.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, adroll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with [company website]. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of adroll and their partners? Targeted advertising.

 **Other times we may collect personal information**  
From time to time, genoahc may conduct surveys and contests via this Site, email, other media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.

 **How we use your personal information?**  
Information we collect on genoahc may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:

Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online. Register you as a member of genoahc. Prevent fraud and bill you for your purchases. Confirm your orders. Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests. Communicate great values and featured items to you. Find and stock the products you want. Customize your purchase experience How is your information protected?

We use the latest in encryption technology, including 128 bit SSL encryption to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception. We employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas. We maintain a rigorous hiring process to screen out potential employees with criminal backgrounds. All employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities. We also have back up servers and power supplies to guard against power outages and other natural occurrences that could pose a threat to the integrity of your personal information. Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account. Once an account has been terminated, measures are taken to remove those users from the system who no longer need access to our system.

When an employee is terminated or is no longer with the company, we change the access codes that the employee used to access any customer accounts. Account login sessions are terminated after three failed login attempts; all terminated login sessions are logged for follow-up. Passwords must contain at least six characters, one of which is non-alphanumeric. Unused customer accounts, those that have shown no activity for 6 months are purged from our systemwhen and with whom can we share your personal information?

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with this Site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; storing, sharing and retrieving customers' photo images in our Photo Center; enhancing and improving clients' purchase experience; enabling access to our partners' web sites; providing a personalized purchase experience; preventing fraud and completing payment method processing. Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required to prevent harm or injury (such as product recalls, fraud, claims or other liability) or to comply with valid legal processes (subpoenas, warrants) or as required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

 **How can you control the use of your personal information?**  
You can modify or delete your personal information anytime. Simply go to My genoahc. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. Do not share Your genoahc password with anyone. Other than on this Site, genoahc will never ask you for your password.

 **How does genoahc secure information collected?**  
This Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as:  
* Safeguarding all financial transactions done through this Site with Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") encryption   
* Granting only employees who are providing a specific service access to your personal information   
* Working only with third-party service providers who we believe adequately secure all computer hardware.   
While our business is designed with safeguarding your personal information in mind, please remember that 100% security does not presently exist anywhere, online or offline.

 **More about your privacy**  
We realize that making purchases at genoahc, or any other web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our clients that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address or checking account information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally. We believe that you have a right to know, before purchase at genoahc or at any other time, exactly what information we might collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it.

We do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. You have the right to control your personal information as you see fit.

If you have an account at genoahc and you want to change, modify or delete any of your personal information, you can do so anytime by going to My genoahc. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.

Genoahc may provide links to certain third party web sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to activities conducted and personal information collected on this genoahc web site. Other web sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and security.

Genoahc will obtain your consent before allowing the download of any software from the genoahc Site, and genoahc will not automatically download any software to your computer system. Once you consent to the initial download of any software, you may receive automatic updates or patches pertaining to such software. You understand and agree that any material, including but not limited to downloaded software, required or automated updates, modifications, genoahc, or software otherwise obtained through the use of the genoahc web Site is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damages to your computer system or loss of data that may result from any such material.
